<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on  </title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on  </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>Powered By Hugo &amp; Blogdown - Theme Minimo </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking At The Largest 100 Churches In America</title>
      <link>/post/exploring-the-largest-100-churches-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/exploring-the-largest-100-churches-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Each year, Outreach Magazine and Lifeway Research colloborate to produce the “Outreach 100.” The two companies survey churches, verify data, and then compile lists of the fastest growing churches and the largest churches in America. They’ve recently made some of this information available for free on their website.
I wanted to visualize some of their data. Every church on the “Outreach 100” has an HTML Table associated with it. Using R I was able to arrange the HTML tables into something more useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Trends &amp; Ulysses S. Grant</title>
      <link>/post/i-m-sorry-i-didn-t-know-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/i-m-sorry-i-didn-t-know-that/</guid>
      <description>“Write three things you learned about Ulysses S. Grant that you didn’t already know before taking this class.”
Roughly 100 college students responded to this prompt on their latest assignment in an American History II class I teach.
Their top answer: “I didn’t know Grant was a president.”
It’s not that important to know that Ulysses S. Grant was a president before taking an American History class. Knowledge of presidential facts is not an accurate measurement of anyone’s intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Are Naming Their Children After Creed Bratton</title>
      <link>/post/kramer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kramer/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve used the internet this year, you’re likely aware of the fact that people are naming their children after popular characters from HBO’s Game of Thrones.
The data shows that no one in America named their child Daenerys before show’s debut in 2011. By 2016, more than 100 families were choosing the name Daenerys. The memes are coming to life! Working from the ever-popular babynames dataset, I wanted to see if people were naming their children after characters that closely follow the Game of Thrones pattern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People are naming their children after Creed Bratton.</title>
      <link>/test_post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/test_post/</guid>
      <description>true  If you’ve used the internet this year, you’re likely aware of the fact that people are naming their children after popular characters from HBO’s Game of Thrones.
Maybe you’ve seen a chart like this:
In 2016, more than 100 children were named after Daenerys.
This Game of Thrones experiment is pretty popular for one obvious reason:
No one named their child Daenerys before show’s debut in 2011. It’s safe to conclude that the show was responsible for the child’s name and identity going forward in life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>