<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on  </title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on  </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright> </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking At The Largest 100 Churches In America</title>
      <link>/post/exploring-the-largest-100-churches-in-america/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/exploring-the-largest-100-churches-in-america/</guid>
      <description>Each year, Outreach Magazine publishes the “Outreach 100.” Lifeway Research and Outreach Magazine colloborate to survey churches, verify the data, and then compile lists. Their annual reports detail the fastest growing churches in America and the largest chuches in America. A lot of the information is available for free on their website.
The data on the website is great, but I wanted to visualize what was available for free in a different way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Sorry I Didn&#39;t Know That</title>
      <link>/post/i-m-sorry-i-didn-t-know-that/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/i-m-sorry-i-didn-t-know-that/</guid>
      <description>“Write three things you learned about Ulysses S. Grant that you didn’t already know before taking this class.”
Roughly 100 college students responded to this prompt on their latest assignment in an American History II class I teach.
Their top answer: “I didn’t know Grant was a president.”
It’s not that important to know that Ulysses S. Grant was a president before taking an American History class. Knowledge of presidential facts is not an accurate measurement of anyone’s intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Will this get tagged to blog?</title>
      <link>/post/will-this-get-tagged-to-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/will-this-get-tagged-to-blog/</guid>
      <description>So does this pull to blog?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>People Are Naming Their Children After Creed Bratton</title>
      <link>/post/kramer/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/kramer/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve used the internet this year, you’re likely aware of the fact that people are naming their children after popular characters from HBO’s Game of Thrones.
Maybe you’ve seen a chart like this:
In 2016, more than 100 children were named after the Game of Thrones character Daenerys.
No one named their child Daenerys before show’s debut in 2011. It’s safe to conclude that the show was responsible for the child’s name and identity going forward in life.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>